<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<chatter>
    <issue date="May 23, 2007" url="0523">
        <articles>
            <article id="sharons-corner">
                <title>Sharon&#8217;s Corner</title>
                <intro>On Thursday, May 10, 2007, Brookhaven College had more than 180 graduates celebrate their accomplishment of earning an associate degree or certificate.  In attendance were the graduates&#8217; family members, friends and co-workers who came to honor their achievements.</intro>
                <body>
                    <p>On Thursday, May 10, 2007, more than 180 Brookhaven College graduates celebrated their accomplishment of earning an associate degree or certificate.  In attendance were the graduates&#8217; family members, friends and co-workers who came to honor their achievements.  Once again, thanks to all of you who helped to make this graduation exercise a special occasion for our graduates and their families and supporters.  Very special thanks go to <b>Stephen Roberts</b>, student speaker, <b>Christina Garza</b>, student invocation presenter, and <b>Bob Ferguson</b>, DCCCD Board Trustee.</p>
                    <p>The end of the spring semester and the beginning of the summer terms are very special times of the year.  Student graduates are ending one chapter of their lives while beginning another.  Employees begin to experience closure of an academic year, while beginning the rejuvenation process and preparation for the beginning of another year.   The summer is often seen as a transitional period and this year is no different.</p>
                    <p>Dr. <b>Claude Caffee</b>, vice president for student development, will retire effective Aug. 31.  He has contributed more than 25 years of service to Brookhaven College.  He is a highly respected leader and student advocate.  We will begin the search process for the position of vice president of enrollment services and student success with a vacancy notice that will be advertised this summer.  A search committee consisting of staff members, students and faculty will be chaired by <b>Brenda Dalton</b>, director of advising and Texas Success Initiative.  The committee will begin its work in early September and will conclude its work with a recommendation to the DCCCD Board of Trustees no later than December.  Dr. Caffee has agreed to assist the college with the transition by working part time until the search is concluded in December.</p>
                    <p>Dr. <b>Derek Mpinga</b>, vice president of instruction, has accepted another position and submitted his resignation effective June 30.  We thank him for his dedication and commitment to education and wish him much success with his new position.  Dr. <b>Richard McCrary</b>, associate vice chancellor for educational affairs for academic programs, has agreed to serve as Brookhaven College&#8217;s interim vice president of learning and student success, beginning July 1, as we make the transition in our instructional area. Dr. McCrary has held a variety of positions in the DCCCD over the last 35 years: counselor, instructor, director of counseling, and a number of positions at the District Office including his present position of associate vice chancellor of educational affairs for academic programs.  During his District Office tenure, he has served as an interim vice president at Cedar Valley, Mountain View, and Richland colleges.  In addition, he served for a year as the interim vice chancellor of educational affairs.  He holds a B.S. and M.Ed. from East Texas State University, now Texas A&amp;M at Commerce, an Ed.D. in community college education from Nova Southeastern University, and has additional graduate work at the University of Alabama, the University of Illinois, and The Ohio State University.  Dr. McCrary has extensive experience in providing leadership to a number of districtwide initiatives and is exceedingly familiar with curriculum issues impacting the DCCCD. We look forward to Dr. McCrary joining our team as we continue to strengthen our instructional area based on the learning college concept.</p>
                    <p>Other transitions occurring this summer include welcoming new faculty joining our &#8220;family&#8221; in the fall semester.  New faculty beginning with the fall 2007 semester, contingent on Board approval, include <b>Jim Dudlo</b>, history; <b>Melody Gamblin-Bullock</b>, music, and <b>Geoffrey Saari</b>, English.  Other faculty positions approved in the Planning and Budget process include two visiting scholar positions in English and child development.</p>
                    <p>Other personnel requests approved for the new fiscal year include the following.</p>
                    <p>Visiting Scholar Administator - Associate Dean, Distance Learning</p>
                    <p>Conversion of an EMS Clinical Coordinator from part to full time</p>
                    <p>Conversion of a Music Department Assistant III from part to full time (CB9)</p>
                    <p>Conversion of Business Studies Instructional Associate from part to full time (T35)</p>
                    <p>World Languages Coordinator, Instructional Learning Lab (TL7)</p>
                    <p>Human Resources Assistant II (CG4)</p>
                    <p>College Transcript Evaluator (CS5)</p>
                    <p>Academic Advisor (TK8)</p>
                    <p>Part-time Counseling funds - $30,000</p>
                    <p>Part-time Department Assistant Testing Center - $15,500</p>
                    <p>Planning and Organizational Learning Specialist (N70)</p>
                    <p>Part-time Tutoring funds - $30,000</p>
                    <p>Although there were more than $442,000 of personnel requests and only $370,500 available, through discussion and collaboration all 14 personnel requests were approved.  Thank you to the Planning and Budget Committee for its work and special &#8220;kudos&#8221; to <b>George Herring</b> for working with the budget to help the college meet its personnel needs.</p>
                    <p>As usual, Brookhaven continues to excel in many venues.  Congratulations to the Marketing and Public Information Office for receiving the First Place Awards for Continuing Education Web Page and Special Promotional Event at the Annual Spring conference of Texas Association of Continuing Education, TACE.</p>
                    <p>Special commendation goes to <b>Joy Bailey</b>, program director continuing education and the Alternative Certification of Teachers, ACT, Advisory Committee for the reinstatement of the Brookhaven program to full accreditation status.</p>
                    <p>Once again, thanks goes to everyone who participated in the trivia games to support the textbook fund.  A special thanks to organizer <b>Nita Drescher</b>; quiz developer <b>Terri Edrich</b> and all the volunteers who helped make the day a big success.  The $1,500 collected will help many students with book support as they strive to make their dream a reality.</p>
                    <p>Several weeks ago I asked for volunteers to serve on the Brookhaven College Quality Enhancement Plan, QEP, team.  Although we had some volunteers, it is important that we assemble the best group that will lead the topic selection and development of the plan that will be submitted to SACS.  Thank you to all that have taken an interest with this plan.  An announcement regarding the committee members will be coming soon.</p>
                    <p>With spring showers come May flowers; may your flowers bloom and bring you much joy as we begin our summer season!</p>
                </body>
            </article>
            <article id="see-commencement-2007">
                <title>See Commencement 2007</title>
                <intro>Though not everyone at the college interacts with students on a daily basis, everyone can take pride in the accomplishments of students on a special day like Commencement.</intro>
                <body>
                    <p>Though not everyone at the college interacts with students on a daily basis, everyone can take pride in the accomplishments of students on a special day like Commencement.  This year, hundreds of students celebrated with family, friends and the college, as they crossed the stage to receive their congratulations and diplomas or certificates.</p>
                    <p>Congratulations also go to some of our Brookhaven brethren who took those same steps as well.  <b>Christine Broadus</b> and <b>Milan McGowan</b> earned Associate of Arts degrees.  <b>Maribel Pullen</b> completed her Associate of Science degree.</p>
                    <p>This year&#8217;s Minnie Stevens Piper Nominee, <b>Cynthia Mills</b>, delivered the commencement address, after a welcome from president, Dr. <b>Sharon L. Blackman</b> and greetings from trustee <b>Bob Ferguson</b>.  Music from the Faculty and Student Orchestra as well as the Vocal Jazz Ensemble rounded out much of the evening&#8217;s celebrations.</p>
                    <p>If you weren&#8217;t able to attend, these photos can offer a sense of the event and of our student&#8217;s celebration.</p>
                </body>
            </article>
            <article id="ifort-worth-weeklyi">
                <title><i>Fort Worth Weekly</i> Features Book Buy-Back Perspectives from Brookhaven Student and Faculty</title>
                <intro>The latest edition of the <i>Fort Worth Weekly</i> includes an article focusing on the continuing battle students face in affording and re-selling textbooks.  &#8220;Buy-Back Blues,&#8221; features the comments of several college students.</intro>
                <body>
                    <p>The latest edition of the <i>Fort Worth Weekly</i> includes an article focusing on the continuing battle students face in affording and re-selling textbooks.  &#8220;Buy-Back Blues,&#8221; features the comments of several college students, including Lauri Wiss, a Brookhaven College student, who has lobbied in Austin for legislation that would prevent publishers from updating textbook editions more than once every three years.  Wiss has also gathered signatures at the college on a petition to ask that students be given a textbook &#8220;tax holiday&#8221; like the one that is available for the purchase of clothes and supplies for students each August.</p>
                    <p>The article addresses how publishers &#8220;update&#8221; textbooks for new editions with very few additions or changes.  In addition it talks to professors about the role they play in the process in the books that they select for their courses.  <b>Haven Abedin</b>, English professor, talked to the reporter, I&#8217;sha Gaines, about setting up ways to use the same textbook for successive courses.</p>
                    <p>To gain a fuller understanding of the issues and challenges, students, faculty members and bookstores face read a full edition of the article here. (Link to http://www.fwweekly.com/content.asp?article=4852)</p>
                </body>
            </article>
            <article id="trivia-earns-big">
                <title>Trivia Earns Big Bucks For Book Fund</title>
                <intro>Was it looks, was it charm, or was it just the cash?  The Sofa Kings, led by <b>Greg Jacobs</b>, were the ultimate winners of the Trivia Challenge, bidding $500 for the points that put them over the top.</intro>
                <body>
                    <p>Was it looks, was it charm, or was it just the cash?  The Sofa Kings, led by <b>Greg Jacobs</b>, were the ultimate winners of the Trivia Challenge, bidding $500 for the points that put them over the top. The Trivia Tigers, led by <b>Monica Taliaferro</b>, came close in the bidding offering more than $400, with donations coming in from other tables around the room.</p>
                    <p>Where then did the brains lie, though?  The SPIKES, led by <b>Tarrilynn Wall</b>, took top honors on points alone.  The questions ranged from the colors of the Olympic Circles to Gerald Ford&#8217;s middle name covering sports, entertainment, history, geography, literature and more.  The team who fared the worst received a set of reference books so they could bone-up on their answers for the next challenge.</p>
                    <p>While the winners will have bragging rights for months to come, the real winners at the Trivia Challenge were the students.  The event raised more than $1,500 for the Brookhaven Book Fund that is coordinated and managed by the Faculty Association.  This single fund-raising event will cover approximately half of the funds distributed throughout an academic year.</p>
                    <p>The book fund helps students who need to get textbooks or who need assistance getting materials until their financial aid or next paycheck arrives.  The fund holds textbooks that were donated by professors or that have been purchased with the funds and loans them to students in need.  In addition, copy cards are given to students who need to copy some book pages until they can purchase the book.</p>
                    <p>There were a large number of people involved in making the event a success in addition to all the participants and team leaders.  <b>Bob Smith</b>, PSSA president, inspired the event with a trivia competition, led by <b>Terri Edrich</b>, college director of human resources, at a PSSA potluck.  Terri oversaw the trivia itself choosing categories and questions and recruiting the scorekeepers.  <b>Nita Drescher</b>, developmental reading professor, coordinated the trivia teams themselves.  Others like, <b>Carrie Schweitzer</b>, <b>Susan Osgood</b>, Facilities Services, <b>Lynne Levesque</b>, <b>Jane Quetin</b> and the Human Resources Office staff pitched in to pull it all together.</p>
                </body>
            </article>
            <article id="notes-from-the">
                <title>Notes from the PSSA</title>
                <intro>Submitted by Bob Smith</intro>
                <intro>Keep up with the latest association news in the Professional Support Staff Association&#8217;s contribution to the Courtyard Chatter.  Check on meeting dates, good news from members and see who is in the member spotlight this week.</intro>
                <body>
                    <p>Submitted by Bob Smith, president of the PSSA</p>
                    <p>MISSION STATEMENT</p>
                    <p><em>The PSSA exists to enhance the overall work environment of the Brookhaven College Professional Support Staff, assist the student body through scholarships and other endeavors  and work to uphold the image of Brookhaven College in general.</em></p>
                    <p>CONGRATULATIONS TO OUR MEMBERS</p>
                    <p>Courtney Chambers, a great niece of <strong>Pat Byars</strong>, a Friend of the PSSA, has been accepted into the School of Journalism Honors Program at the University of Missouri.  Go Tigers!</p>
                    <p>Bridget Lynch, daughter of <strong>Laurey Lynch</strong> has been awarded the St. Edward&#8217;s Trustee&#8217;s Distinguished Scholar Award as well as other academic scholarships.  Bridget will be attending St. Edward&#8217;s University this fall after attending Brookhaven College this summer.</p>
                    <p>Bridget has just cut her waist length hair to donate to &#8220;Locks of Love,&#8221; an organization that processes human hair into wigs for financially disadvantaged children who experience long-term hair loss due to medical conditions such as alopecia areata and from chemo treatments for cancer.</p>
                    <p>Andrea Lundy, granddaughter of <strong>Arlene Pike</strong>, for whom the Homolopsis Pikeae was named, will graduate this month from Joshua High School in Joshua, Texas, with a near perfect grade point average! She is graduating in the top tier of her class and will attend Columbia College in Chicago this fall; she intends to major in interior design.  Her academic achievements include the publication of two poems.</p>
                    <p>Another of Arlene&#8217;s granddaughters, Sara McClendon will graduate from Buffalo High School, in Buffalo, Mo., later this month.  Sara also is an achiever; she has held the position of class president and student council president, she has had perfect attendance throughout her high school years and will graduate with a near perfect GPA!  In the fall, Sara will be attending Southeast Missouri State University located in Cape Girardeau, Missouri.</p>
                    <p>NEW PSSA MEMBERS &amp; FRIENDS OF THE PSSA</p>
                    <p>New Members:		Joe Sanders in the Admissions Office,</p>
                    <p>Monica Hernandez, working with the FIPSE grant,</p>
                    <p>Jill Williams in School of the Arts,</p>
                    <p>Barbara Szabo in the Police Department, and</p>
                    <p>Donna Baker in Instructional Support and Outreach</p>
                    <p>New FOTP:			Nita Drescher, developmental reading professor, and</p>
                    <p>Nancy Barlow, English professor</p>
                    <p>The PSSA welcomes each of you!</p>
                    <p>NOTE:</p>
                    <p>If you are not a PSSA member or a Friend of the PSSA, you are encouraged to join.  Interested individuals should stop by the Student Services Center, Room S072, and, after paying the $5 dues, Mildred Kelley will add you to the membership roll.</p>
                    <p>MEMBER PROFILE</p>
                    <p>In this issue of the <i>Courtyard Chatter</i> the PSSA recognizes another long-time and very valued PSS employee and PSSA member, <strong>Oscar Valdez</strong>.  Oscar has been employed at Brookhaven for 12 years and actually has three jobs.  First, Oscar is a HVAC technician; he has performed these services for the entire 12 years and he believes he is the best technician on campus. He also holds two part-time college positions. For the past three years he has worked as an assistant in the Corporate and Continuing Education Division where he performs various customer tasks such as assisting students with registration, and in recent months he has taken a second part-time job as a Web developer in Marketing and Public Information Office.  In July when a building has no cool air, I bet we know which of his three areas of expertise will be in the greatest demand!</p>
                    <p>Oscar has an associate degree in air conditioning and heating from Eastfield College and a bachelor&#8217;s degree in computer information systems from Our Lady of The Lake University. (As an aside it must be noted that the educational and training depth of the Brookhaven College PSS is amazing!)</p>
                    <p>Oscar very much enjoys his positions at Brookhaven.  He considers the campus a 	great place to earn an education, considers the people to be very friendly and as a plus, the location is close to his house so he does not care how high gasoline prices go.  During his 12 plus years at Brookhaven, Oscar has seen significant changes and growth.  He has seen the S, J and M buildings being constructed and assisted in the HVAC operations and balancing, which is no easy feat.  He is amazed with the rapid change in computer technology and the effect it has had in his life both personally and professionally.</p>
                    <p>Oscar and his wife, Maria Del Socorro Valdez, live in Richardson and have two boys, Vicente and Emmanuel who are three and one years old, respectively.  While he is not working at one of his three jobs Oscar likes to play football soccer and he also enjoys jogging.  If you watch, you may see him taking advantage of the Brookhaven jogging trail.</p>
                    <p>When you see Oscar around the campus please introduce yourself if you are not acquainted, and ask him about the circumstances surrounding his meeting Earl Campbell of the Houston Oilers.  Is there a possible fourth job in his future?</p>
                    <p>Oscar, thanks for being here!</p>
                    <p>MEETINGS AND OTHER BUSINESS</p>
                    <p>The annual PSSA flower sale was a great success and the PSSA offers its thanks to the entire campus community.  Special thanks goes to those individuals who worked very hard to make it happen and particularly to <strong>Sarah Graifemberg</strong> who spearheaded the event.</p>
                    <p>At the April PSSA meeting, the member attendees voted to contribute funds to the Brookhaven Student Book Fund and the Employees Emergency Fund.  For these and other details please refer to the minutes of the meeting.  These contributions as well as others would not be possible without the support of the PSSA members, the Friends of the PSSA and the college in general.</p>
                    <p>Upcoming events include the monthly PSSA meetings scheduled for May 23, June 21 and July 25.  After June, because of accommodations being made for the Early College High School classes, it may be necessary to move from our usual Room A203 meeting place; you will be notified of any changes.</p>
                    <p>In late May, the PSSA will be conducting a survey of the PSS to gather their input regarding the association and other items of interest.  <strong>Mathewos Kassa</strong> has computerized the survey and will give us a short demonstration at the May 23 meeting; please plan to attend.</p>
                    <p>Our membership continues to grow and we encourage the membership and active involvement of all professional support staff.</p>
                    <p>If anyone has items for inclusion in this column relating to the PSSA, FOTP or members please let me know.</p>
                </body>
            </article>
            <article id="aauw-celebrates-nancy">
                <title>AAUW Celebrates Nancy Strickland</title>
                <intro>A banquet May 1 brought together local community and education leaders to honor Nancy Strickland as a life-long advocate for education.  Strickland was honored with the 2007 Woman Leadership Award from the Farmers Branch/Carrollton American Association of University Women.</intro>
                <body>
                    <p>A banquet May 1 brought together local community and education leaders to honor Nancy Strickland as a life-long advocate for education.  Strickland was honored with the 2007 Woman Leadership Award from the Farmers Branch/Carrollton American Association of University Women.</p>
                    <p>The gala was a fund-raiser for the C-FB AAUW.  The event  raised approximately $6,000 for the C-FB AAUW Educational Foundation, part of which will fund three scholarships of $1,000 each.   AAUW representatives said they are especially grateful to the scholarship donors and to the work of the scholarship committee headed by <b>Marjorie Westberry</b>, English professor in the Communications Division.  Brookhaven College, the C-FB ISD and SHW Group LLP all supported the event.</p>
                    <p>Annette Griffin, superintendent, and John Tepper, president of the board of trustees for the Carrollton-Farmers Branch Independent School District, were just two of the guests along with friends and relatives who shared amusing and heart-felt memories of working with Strickland in the C-FB ISD.  Beginning her teaching career as a substitute during the Asian flu epidemic of 1959, Strickland went on to spend 28 years teaching in the C-FB ISD.  She taught at Farmers Branch Elementary, Vivian Field Middle School, R.L. Turner and Newman Smith high schools and after her retirement continued teaching for the GED program at Mary Grimes School.</p>
                    <p>Strickland&#8217;s friends encouraged her to continue her work in education by running for school board, and she did run in 1995.  She has served four terms for a total of 12 years, before her retirement this month.  Her devotion to educational pursuits led Strickland to become a founding member of the Farmers Branch/Carrollton branch of AAUW in 1975.  She volunteers weekly at R.H. Dedman, and at Reading and Resources for the Blind, and is active in the Kappa Phi chapter of Delta Kappa Gamma, the Rhea Crane Book Club, the Friends of Farmers Branch Manske Library and other service organizations.</p>
                    <p>The new intermediate school on Fyke Road will bear her name when it opens as the Nancy H. Strickland Intermediate School.</p>
                </body>
            </article>
            <article id="thank-you-notes">
                <title>Thank You Notes</title>
                <intro>The President&#8217;s Office received two special thank you notes highlighting some of the outstanding faculty members who have helped and fostered students to reach their goals and to complete their courses successfully.</intro>
                <body>
                    <p><em>The President&#8217;s Office received two special thank you notes highlighting some of the outstanding faculty members who have helped and fostered students to reach their goals and to complete their courses successfully. </em></p>
                    <p>To the office of:</p>
                    <p>President Sharon L. Blackman, Ed D.</p>
                    <p>It is with great pleasure that I am writing this letter to you about a member of your faculty, <strong>Ms. (Marla) Owens</strong> has so impressed me with her abilities as a teacher of developmental mathematics that I felt no other recourse but to let you know of them.</p>
                    <p>During my two-plus-year tenure here at Brookhaven, with the exception of two teachers, I have had plenty of good instructors and a few great ones, yet I have never had an exceptional teacher like the one I&#8217;ve found in Ms. Owens. My transcript should indicate to you the type of student that I am. I take my studies very seriously and my GPA reflects this. With this in mind, my previous teacher in DMAT 0099 had teaching methods that were not productive despite my best effort to understand her.</p>
                    <p>This is not the case with Ms. Owens&#8217; class as I have passed both DMAT 0098 and 0099 without any problems. It also is because of Ms. Owens  that I am completely prepared for the Introduction to Statistics class. Without her patience, her invaluable insight, her ability to prepare us for the material on tests, I, and those who attend with me, would not have had much of a chance at all. Ms. Owens&#8217; amiable nature encourages a synergistic environment that fosters growth while challenging the student to achieve more than they might have thought possible.</p>
                    <p>Ms. Owens deserves recognition for her abilities and I felt the least I could do, was to shine a little light upon some of her accomplishments. Brookhaven College has rarely disappointed me, and certainly with teachers such as Ms. Owens, it has surpassed my expectations. Thank you for providing us with such an invaluable teacher.</p>
                    <p>Sincerely,</p>
                    <p>Solomon Odom</p>
                    <p>Phi Theta Kappa, public affairs officer</p>
                    <p>Dear Dr. Blackman,</p>
                    <p>My wife and I had the good fortune to take a course taught by Ms. Amolisch, POFI 1104 Computer Fundamentals Internet-Advanced.  She has a rare talent to make a subject which could be dry, interesting.</p>
                    <p>You are very fortunate to have her on your faculty.</p>
                    <p>Sincerely,</p>
                    <p>Wm. T. Ward</p>
                </body>
            </article>
        </articles>
        <features>
            <feature id="announcements">
                <title>Announcements</title>
                <announcement id="chatter-switches-to">
                    <title>Chatter Switches to Summer Schedule</title>
                    <body>
                        <p>The <i>Courtyard Chatter</i> is switching to a summer schedule of publication.  We will publish only once a month in June and July with two issues in August.  The publication dates are June 20 and July 18, with deadlines for submissions the Friday prior to publication.</p>
                    </body>
                </announcement>
                <announcement id="consider-summer-camp">
                    <title>Consider Summer Camp at Brookhaven College</title>
                    <body>
                        <p>The Corporate and Continuing Education Division has established summer courses for children.  There is a wide variety of courses to choose from focusing on sports, education, the arts and more.  Look for courses that fit your family's needs and tell your friends as well.</p>
                    </body>
                </announcement>
            </feature>
            <feature id="birthdays" month="June">
                <title>June Birthdays</title>
                <birthday-list>
                    <birthday date="June 1" names="Jason Friedrich, Barbara Jagger, Dennis Maddox, Taft Sickles" />
                    <birthday date="June 4" names="Durhl Caussey, Melody Gamblin-Bullock, Robert Meyer, Carlo Pezzimenti" />
                    <birthday date="June 5" names="John Adcox" />
                    <birthday date="June 6" names="Paschal Egbujor, Leigh Kowalsky" />
                    <birthday date="June 7" names="Keith Umbach" />
                    <birthday date="June 8" names="Hazel Carlos, Chun Leung, Annetta McLelland" />
                    <birthday date="June 9" names="Joy Bailey, Robert Neff" />
                    <birthday date="June 10" names="Heibatollah Behbahani, Terri Canaris, Susana Ruelas, Stephen Schuster" />
                    <birthday date="June 11" names="Francis Brooks, Philip Gabbert, Kjell Johansen" />
                    <birthday date="June 12" names="Troy Cenac" />
                    <birthday date="June 13" names="Charles Close, Glenn Kasparian, Czarina Reyes" />
                    <birthday date="June 14" names="Kellie Hickman, Kathryn Martinez" />
                    <birthday date="June 15" names="Amy Bryant, Mary Henry" />
                    <birthday date="June 17" names="John Hatch" />
                    <birthday date="June 18" names="Daniel Barnard, George Bright, Michael Trubisky" />
                    <birthday date="June 22" names="Roy Allen" />
                    <birthday date="June 23" names="Amy Dillavou" />
                    <birthday date="June 24" names="Peter Abadie, Juan Sanchez" />
                    <birthday date="June 26" names="Alison Winn" />
                    <birthday date="June 28" names="John Gilmer, Daniel Hubbard" />
                    <birthday date="June 30" names="Alma Felix, Nacole Lacey" />
                </birthday-list>
            </feature>
            <feature id="hail-and-farewell">
                <title>Hail And Farewell</title>
                <people for="Hail">
                    <person name="Travis Haapala" department="Marketing and Public Information Office" position="location Web developer I" />
                    <person name="Napoleon Hill" department="Police Department" position="college police officer" />
                    <person name="Raymond Imaican" department="Marketing and Public Information Office" position="location Web developer I" />
                    <person name="Krystle Morrow" department="Police Department" position="police communications operator I" />
                    <person name="Sharon Poole" department="Communications Division" position="department assistant II" />
                    <person name="Joslyn Short" department="Police Department" position="police communications operator I" />
                </people>
                <people for="Farewell">
                    <person name="John Graf" department="Instructional Support &amp; Outreach Services" position="interpreter I" />
                    <person name="Carrie Quackenbush" department="Marketing and Public Information Office" position="location Web developer I" />
                    <person name="Janice Sue St. John" department="Advising and Counseling Center" position="academic advisor II" />
                    <person name="Kelvin Williams" department="Facilities Services" position="groundskeeper" />
                </people>
                <people for="Role Changes">
                    <person name="Dawn Bishop" department="Business Services" position="assistant to the vice president of Business Services" />
                    <person name="Evonne Clark" department="Mathematics and Science Division" position="division secretary" />
                    <person name="Chun Leung" department="Facilities Services" position="HVAC technician" />
                </people>
            </feature>
        </features>
    </issue>
</chatter>
